when you brushed your
когда ты делал чистку
teeth this morning, I don’t mean about
зубов сегодня утром не в смысле про в
professional teeth cleaning in dentistry, you did
стоматологии профессиональную чистку
n’t just brush your teeth. Well,
зубов не просто чистил щёткой Ну я
somewhere, maybe four or 3 months
где-то ну возможно четыре или 3 месяца
ago, I put a filling in. I didn’t brush my teeth. I didn’t
назад ставил пломбу А чистку зубов Не не
do dentistry. Why, why,
делал стоматология А почему Да зачем
if I can clean here?  teeth at
если я могу здесь почистить зубы у
home Hello,
себя Здравствуйте
I enjoy every moment with my heart too Smile,
сердечко наслаждаюсь тоже Улыбнитесь
stand by as you
стойте вы
leave And where do you need me to
отхода А вам откуда нужно чтобы я
be from
был с
Ukraine for you where will I be Where do you
Украины для вас откуда буду Откуда вы
want from where I will be  for
захотите оттуда я и буду для
you not you immediately tell me if you are from
вас не вы сразу скажите если вы с
Ukraine I will not be with you raska no I am not
Украины Я не буду с вами раска не я не
from Ukraine I myself am from Kursk Here I
из Украины я сам с Курска вот Вот у меня
did it Green background I put a flag I
это сделал Зелёный фон подставляю флаг я
communicate as if I installed a VPN They
общаюсь как будто я поставил VPN Они
think that I am theirs and they start
думают что я их и они начинают У них
Today is their Maidan Day, they are starting there
сегодня день Майдана они начинают там
Glory to Ukraine
Слава Украине
of some kind and
некой и
in short, I just don’t want to communicate
короче я просто цами не хочу общаться
with people, so I’m not the same, they’re aggressive, I’m
поэтому с м не я тоже они агрессивные я
just trolling them, so I’m the course And where are you
их только троллю так я сам курс А вы
from Krasnodar oh Krasnodar we are  we've all been on vacation
откуда Краснодар о Краснодар мы отдыхали
in Anapa
в Анапе были
since
так всё вы с самого
Krasnodar itself. Well, we've been living here for 6 years already, but from
Краснодара Ну живём здесь уже 6 лет а с
Samara we didn't do it in Krasnodar. And where is the
Самары делались не в Краснодаре А где и
Malaninsky Autonomous Okrug? Oh my God,
маланинский автономный округ О боже мой
my dad once worked there, he
у меня батя когда-то там работал там
said it was so cold, it's just brutal. Yes,
говорил холодина такая просто жесть Да
there we have  It’s already frosty Yes, he’s these,
там у нас уже морозы Да он эти
in short, he was this researcher, he
он короче был этим исследователем он
biolo
биоло
they went There are such birds,
они ездили Там есть такие птицы тухта
you know, you know, they explored
знаете знаю Вот они исследовали
the Tukhta, the Sun understood There, just when the period
тухта ВС поняла Там как раз когда риод
they have very
размножения у них этих у турнов очень
interesting mating dances, they
брачные танцы интересные они фильмы
recorded films, he was this tukhta.
записывали он вот этот тухта
It’s clear He had a dissertation on them
был Понятно У него диссертация по ним
on turukhtan. I’m at home with photographs. A bunch of them, the
была по турухтан Я дома фотографии Куча
whole apartment was covered with fabric of these
у на вся квартира была обклеена тка этих
hennas, what did they do
хнов что делали
there, well, I was actually born there, as it were
там ну я там родилась вообще как бы там
I studied there, as it were, and what
я от училась как бы ну а родители кем
did my parents work for? Well, my parents are actually
работали Ну родители у меня вообще по
Moldova by nationality. Neya, they came
национальности Молдова Нея они приехали
in those days, as it were, my dad
в те времена как бы туда вот у меня папа
worked there, as it were.  ventilation shaft in the
работал по вентиляционной шахте в
sports complex Mom I have an ordinary
спортивном комплексе Мама у меня обычный
cook you once saw a live Turukhtan
поварня вы когда-то живого турухтан
no no only from the film you know
видели нет нет только по фильме знаете
what you have there yes yes yes me father Well,
да что там у вас да да да меня отец Ну
they
они
brought me here to Kursk because
привозили сюда в Курск де в том что в
they have an institute of biology in Kursk
Курске у них институт биологический
and they brought two
факультет и они на биофаг привозили две
pairs of turukhtans to the biophage, they’re just so straight forward,
пары турухтан это просто такие аж прямо
they’re really
они машины
class machines. Well, they sort of examined them on
прям класс Ну они их типа исследовали о
the Koltseva and took them back there
кольцева и увезли назад туда
and
а
yeah, it’s clear what you
угу понятно Чем
’re doing, yeah  than work home work home
занимаетесь да чем работа дом работа дом
And who
А кем
do you work with I work in with in
работаете Я работаю в с в
this medicine warehouse warehouse with
этом лекарственном складе склад с
medicines health service collector storekeeper
лекарств здравсервис сборщик кладовщик
What is it now with medicines after the sanction is it
Что сейчас с лекарствами после санкции
normal or
нормально или
not well with medicines it’s normal
нет ну с лекарствами это нормально
orders like
заказы как бы
Oira My mother works as a nurse in a
ойра У меня мама медсестрой работает в
hospital, she says that  Now there are problems
больнице то говорит что сейчас проблемы
with
с
supplies and look where you even say that
поставками а смотр куда даже говори что
this is there, like, well, sodium chloride,
вот это там типа ну хлорид натрий вот
these saline solutions, that’s all there is, that’s all
эти физ растворы это всё есть да это всё
And there are no imported medicines, yes with these
А импортных лекарств не стало да с этими
Yes, I don’t argue Yes with
Да не спорю Да с
[music]
[музыка]
ECT so far with these
ЭСТ пока вот с этими
we have them right there, even if they are delivered,
у нас прям их там даже если привозят то
they are just as it was and they are not there,
их прям сразу как было так и нету всё
she said even
она говорила даже вот
this one, well, maybe you can’t do that,
этот ну как бы так может нельзя делать
but they prescribe pills for patients, there aren’t
да но выписывают таблетки пациентам не
enough for everyone and For example, it is necessary  so that the
хватает на всех и Например нужно чтобы
patient takes two tablets, so two in the
пациент принял две таблетки так вот две
morning, two in the evening, but there’s not enough for everyone
утром две вечером а на всех не хватает
in the department, the doctor can’t
на отделении врач не может же выдать
give it to half and give it to the other half. They say you’re not
половине выдать а половине Говорят вы не
Petya,
Пете да
and he can’t give one tablet at a time
и по одной таблетке не может выдать
because well, he’ll say it’s allotted as many as two, then
потому что ну скажет положен аж две то
they’ll take  calcium gluconate Well chalk actually
берут глюконат кальций Ну мел фактически
Yes and they give one tablet of this one
Да и дают одну таблетку такую одну
calcium gluconate To each of them two, that is,
глюконата кальция Каждому по две то есть
everyone sees that there are two He drinks but they drink
каждый видит что две Он пьёт но пьют по
one of these sanctions Yes yes this is
одну вот такое из этих санкций Да да это
of course terrible of
конечно ужасно
course And what other medications do you have missing
конечно А какие пропали ещё у вас эти
oh honestly  I do
лекарства ой честно я
n’t remember the names, I won’t lie and I won’t
по названиям не помню не буду врать и не
name them now, well, there are some drugs
назову сейчас ну есть такие препараты
that
которые
have disappeared and vitamins are at least
пропали а витамины хоть нормально
sold there normally, vitamins Yes, the local
продаются там витамины Да это местные
production of vitamin rev will surprise How
производство витамино реви удивит Как
they did it like that in the Soviet Union  Vitru,
делали При Советском Союзе так витру вот
these are all sorts of ascorbic acids,
эти вот всякие аскорбинки
they eat me, the word
это они есть меня аж кисло ста слово
ascorbic acid is sour, and the insulin they say is gone too,
аскорбинки а инсулин говорят пропал тоже
yes, there is
да
no insulin, in my opinion,
инсулин нет по-моему
insulin in tablets, you mean in general
инсулин в таблетках имеете в виду вообще
in any
в любом в любой
form, no, in my opinion, insulin, I remember
форме нет по-моему инсулин я вот помню
when I collected insulin  I think
когда я собирала инсулин по-моему в
we still have it in ampoules, but it’s not enough Yes, but
ампулах есть ещё у нас но мало Да но
you still have a little insulin in the floors
инсулин вам полах ещё
Well, you see how it turns out less
есть Ну тут видишь как получается меньше
here, how in nature
тут как в природе регулируется меньше
less insulin is regulated less diabetics less
инсулина меньше диабетиков меньше
diabetics more
диабетиков больше
insulin  They are cruel in the Kremlin, my
инсулина жестоко они в Кремле вот у меня
mother, too, she gets paid, I don’t know how much you
мама тоже она получает не знаю скоко вы
work in a government institution, yes. And my mother is a nurse
работаете да А у меня мама медсестрой
in a regional
вот в областной
hospital. Her salary is 40,000
больнице У неё зарплата 40.000
rubles. Yes, I have the
руб Да у меня в принципе
same thing, and she says that I
также и она говорит это я всю жизнь
have worked all my life, I have experience.  Yes, and I had to study
проработала стаж есть да и учиться надо
And in general,
было И вообще и
he says 40,000 now, I don’t know how it is with
говорит 40.000 сейчас р не знаю как у
you, but what is your nationality, well,
вас а вы вообще кто по национальности ну
it turns out my father is Armenian, my father is
получается у меня отец он армянин отец
Armenian And my mother  from Georgia, Georgian, well,
армянин А мама из Грузии грузинка ну
that’s why I say that there is a little bit,
поэтому я и говорю что есть немножко ну
a little accent, poetic, yes, well, how
маленький акценти поэто с есть да ну как
would we speak Russian in the family? Yes,
бы мы говорим по-русски в семье Да
because, well, it would be customary from the Soviet
потому что ну как бы так с Советского
Union, I was born in the eighty-first
Союза принято бы я восемьдесят первого
year Yes, but still  My
года рождения ещё Да но всё равно у меня
father speaks like this with a strong accent, and my mother speaks like this with a strong accent, so
отец сильно с акцентом говорит так а
many people see that you know, how
многие видят что вот знаете Как бы мне
lucky I am that I have a more
мне ещё повезло что у меня более
Slavic appearance, so I
Славянская внешность получилась так я
take after my mother, here are the Georgians, they are
более в маму пошёл вот грузины Они же
there  more like the Slavs because my
там более на славян похожи во потому что
dad He’s so dark and clearly
папа Он у меня такой тёмный явно
expressed Well, he’s like from Armenia and he’s a
выраженный Ну типа из Армении и он
catfish. I also seem to have been born in Russia, but
сом Я тоже вроде в России родилась но
my parent is from Moldova and
родитель у меня с Молдавии
understood Oh, and you have it like, like, because
понял Ой а у вас там как типа потому что
here in Kursk now in general  It’s not calm
у нас в Курске сейчас вообще не спокойно
there, at least it’s calm in Krasnodar,
у вас там хоть спокойно в Краснодар
it’s calm there now they say it’s flying
спокойно там сейчас говорят прилетает
everywhere, the Americans have already given these
всюду уже ещё американцы дали эти ракеты
long-range missiles in the know, in the know Yes, we have a
дальние в курсе в курсе Да у нас
neighboring Bryansk region, then Ay
соседняя Брянская область то Ай
ran away like that, yes, I’m from Kursk
убежала вот так да да я из Курска
In short, mom  I also have a nurse who
Короче мама У меня тоже медсестра
tells me Yes yes yes, look when you
рассказывает Да да да по смотрите когда
talk to Russians about you being from Ukraine And what do
россиянам говориш ты из Украины А что у
you have there with these medications, they
вас там с этими с лекарствами они все
still aren’t everything is fine, everything is fine With
таки не не всё нормально всё нормально С
shmi dada yes And when you talk about I’m from
шми дада да А когда ты говоришь о Я из
Russia, I have a mother and  everything is completely
России у меня мама и всё совсем
different
по-другому
Hello Hello,
Привет Здравствуйте Вы
where are you from Russia from
откуда с России с
Russia from Russia I understand and the World Cup
России с России понял а ЧМ общаетесь
the Russians are talking about nothing Let’s talk about nothing
россияне ни о чём Давайте ни о чём
Let’s How are you doing? So this is already About
Давайте Как дела у вас нет так это уже О
something It’s About business and  we need to talk about nothing Well,
чём-то это О делах а нужно ни о чём Ну о
we can talk about nothing, we can talk about nothing and
чём можем пообщаться ни о чём а ни о чём
just sit about
просто посидеть
nothing, let’s talk to someone, it
да давайте луча ком-то пообщаемся это
will be the smartest conversation with
будет самый умный разговор с
the Russians, seriously
россиянами серьёзно
What do you have there, a live broadcast or something, yes
Да что у вас там прямой эфир что ли да
about the war, yes Again Who is to blame no  here everything is
о войне да Опять Кто виноват нет тут всё
clearly
ясно
to blame Well, I don’t
виновата Ну не знаю ну а какие у тебя
know, but what kind of thoughts do you have? I don’t even know who is to blame, to be
винова даже не знаю если
honest, but I have such a question, you can
честно но у меня такой вопрос есть можно
ask you are asking permission Yes of
задать вы спрашиваете разрешение Да
course Let’s give permission I’m
конечно Давайте разрешаю Я сегодня
kind today Thank you
добрый Спасибо
What’s the point of you sitting like this
А в чём смысл вы сидите вот так вот и
communicate Who do you want to
общаетесь Кому вы хотите что-либо
prove something to? I don’t want to prove anything to anyone,
доказать никому не хочу доказать ничего
I’m just enjoying myself because you sit and
я просто кайфую а то то что вы сидите и
prove that Ukraine is right, I’m from
доказываете то что Украина права я из
Belarus anyway, where am I from Belarus, the
Белоруси вообще где Я из Беларуссии
city of Gomel And from Belarus
город Гомель А из Беларуси
I apologize, I find these and just
извиняюсь я нахожу этих и просто
mock them
издеваюсь над ними
but in this way, I rise up on my own,
а по таким образом Я само возвышаюсь
self-affirm,
самоутверждаются
Okay, I understand, I understand, well, normal
Хорошо я понял понял ну нормальная же
tactics, I
тактика
really don’t
правда не
know. Well, why and what are the disadvantages? Well, a
знаю Ну а почему а какие минусы
waste of time is actually better to  a
Ну трата времени лучше на самом деле к
psychologist to go to a psychologist, it’s a lot of
психологу сходить психологу это сколько
money to eat there, sit there,
пое туда посиди бабки потратишь Он зато
you’ll spend money, but he’ll cure Ade. But he’ll insult you, but the psychologist won’t insult you, so here I’m insulting, I can’t insult a psychologist. But here I’m insulting, insulting. It’s clear then what you’re talking about here, I just
тогда о чём общаетесь тут я только
came in just now, I’m bored. What do you
сейчас зашёл только сейчас скучал Как вы
think?  What city are you from?
счита вы с какого города
Tver Tver Tver like Afanasy
вообще твер Тверь Твери как Афанасий
Nikitin And you are straight from Belarus right in
Никитин А вы прямо из Беларуси прямо в
Belarus right now  Gomel yes and the Sun Well,
Беларуси сейчас пря Гомель да а ВС Ну
how is the village near Gomel now
как деревня под гомелем сейчас на дачу
I went to the dacha for the
поехал на
weekend how Belarus generally live
выходные как Беларуси вообще проживае
normally Now we’ll drive away the mustachioed one
нормально Вот сейчас усатого прогоним в
next year
следующем году
and we’ll go to the European Union You’re talking about
и будем в Евросоюз идти Вы же про
Lukashenko And you
Лукашенко А вы ещё каких-то усатых
don’t know any other mustachios about
знаете нет про
Lukashenko I
Лукашенко всё
understand everything And  what is it, I did
понял А что такое
n’t just
не просто
ask, I just know only one
спросил просто я только одного
president and all of which Putin is not the
президента знаю и вс какого Путина не
president, he’s a slave owner,
президент это рабовладелец
well, he’s been holding the country for how many
ну он страну держит уже сколько
years, I don’t know why you’re two  ra
лет не знаю зачем ты два ра
you repeat, come on
повторяешь подите
Well, well, we want everything for what we wanted We
Ну Ну всё хотим за то мы хотели Мы
elected Lukashenko in the elections before this
избрали Лукашенко на выборах перед этим
And now we want to change him, I understand,
А теперь мы его хотим поменять я понял
well, I like the fact that we have Putin And I do
ну мне нравится то что у нас Путин А чем
n’t know why Putin likes I don’t have any appeal for him at all.
Путин не знаю У меня на него зва вообще
that's what you did,
никакого нету не А вот что сделал Ты
what year were you
какого года
born? 2001 2001 that is, look, you were
рождения 2001 2001 то есть смотри ты
completely born under Putin, so that is,
полностью родился при Путине так то есть
no, Medvedev was still in this world, it was
нет Медведев же ещё был вро это это
Putin, it was sort of formally set
Путин был это типа формально поставили
bear
медведе
the Constitution, so look, it turns out that
Конституцию так смотри получается что
you lived this entire Putin’s reign, all
вот ты жил это всё правление Путина всё
his policies, you can say what Russia has achieved,
его политика можешь сказать что добилась
what Russia has achieved. Well, I can’t
Россия что добилась Россия Ну я не могу
say anything, how much is your
ничего сказать сколько у тебя
salary?  I
зарплата достаточно живу ну сколько ну
work in a factory as a metal worker
заводе на заводе работаю кем по металлу
and you have 700 dollars.
и 700 долларов имеешь
You were somewhere abroad. No, I don’t want to.
ты был где-то за границей Нет я не хочу
Why don’t I want to just fly to Japan?
А почему не хочу в Японию только слетать
Why don’t you want to go anywhere else later?
А почему не хочешь потом никуда больше
Well, what’s the point? Well, why? Some people go
Ну а смысл Ну почему Одни люди ездят за
abroad, like Peskov, Yes, Lavrov went,
границу вот Песков ездил Да Лавров ездил
all the rich people go, But it makes no sense to you,
все богачи ездят А тебе смысла нет
why? Well, that’s the kind of person I am, they can
почему Ну такой я вот человек они могут
afford it, I
себе позволить я не
can’t, but
могу а
you, you can’t afford it.  Or you don’t
вы ты не можешь себе позволить Или ты не
want to go, you don’t need it, I
хочешь ехать тебе это не нужно не я не
can’t
могу себе
afford it, so it has to be postponed, and here
позволить так это надо откладывать а тут
you pay for food for clothes, it’s
ты за плату отдаёшь за еду за одежду
terrible Well, it’s like that for everyone I
ужас Ну у всех же
mean, everyone Well, except for the rich
так В смысле у все Ну кроме у богатых
Of course, what do you think Where is better?  live in
Конечно а как ты счита Где лучше жить в
Russia or  in
России или в
Europe Well, I would answer That in Russia
Европе Ну я бы ответил То что в России
because I live in Russia but I can
потому что я живу в России но могу
answer that in Europe but also in Europe there
ответить то что и в Европе но и в Европе
are disadvantages again where is the best
есть свои минусы ещё раз где лучший
standard of living in Europe or Russia Russia
уровень жизни в Европе или России России
and why Well I like it here I am here
а почему Ну мне здесь нравится Я здесь
didn't you grow up like that? Yes, for example,
вырос не так это ты вырос Да например
are you there
там ли вы
too How can I answer your question
тоже Как я могу ответить на ваш вопрос
If I haven't even been abroad I
Если я даже не был за границей Я же не
can't understand how good it is Where where
могу понять как хорошо Где где лучше
people live better in Russia or in
живут люди в России или в
Africa of course in Russia Stop Have you been  in
Африке конечно в России Стоп А ты был в
Africa no saw seen see That is, you
Африке нет видел видел видишь То есть ты
immediately clearly said You  I saw the video, yes,
сразу чётко сказал Ты видел видео да Ну
well, you saw about Europe. What other incidents are there
ты же и про Европу видел Какие случи же
about Africa? Well, wait, wait,
ещё ходят об Африке ну подожди Подожди
look. That is, I caught you beautifully. I have
смотри То есть я тебя красиво поймал ты
n’t been to Europe. Yes, that’s why you have
Я ж не был в Европе Да поэто и ты в
n’t been to Africa either, but you’re not talking about Africa, not in
Африке не был но про Африку ты не не в
Russia.  yes And when you ask
России да А когда тебя спрашиваешь
Compare Europe and RUSSIA you
Сравни Европу и РОСИ ты
start Okay then okay I’ll answer
начинаешь Хорошо тогда ладно я отвечу на
your question I would fly to Japan I
ваш вопрос я полетел бы в Японию я бы
wouldn’t live there But where in Europe or
там бы жил бы не А вот где в Европе или
Russia is the best standard of
в России лучший уровень
living  in Europe or in
жизни в Европе или в
Russia Well, probably in Europe Why did you think for so
России Ну наверное в Европе А что так
long?
долго
Well, did you compare everything? Why did you compare
думал Ну сравнивал всё А что ты сравнил
salaries? How do they live there?
зарплату Как живут они там
But there are also some disadvantages, I’m
Но есть же и свои минусы я вот вам
telling you what are the disadvantages in Europe
говорю а какие минусы в Европе по
compared to Russia; in Europe, medicine is
сравнению с Россией в Европе медицина
generally very  dear, not in Russia
вообще очень дорогая не в России вообще
there is no
нет
medicine at all in Russia there is no medicine
медицины в России нет медицины
talking about what they will do for you for free in the
говор что тебе за бесплатно сделают в
hospital Yes, they did it for free,
больни Да ВС сдела бесплатно
of course, and it’s all good when they
ставит конечно и всё это же хорошо когда
give you an enema, not you, you smiled
клизму ставят вам не ты ты улыбнулся
No, well, dentistry is free here,
Да не ну стоматология у нас бесплатная
I’m not looking at that  everyone here  the second one in
же не я смотрю ту тут каждый второй в
chat roulette with teeth I understand that
чат рулетке с зубами Я понимаю что
dentistry is really free Well,
стоматология действительно бесплатна Ну
it’s their own fault then Why am I asking
это уже их же вина то Почему Я спрашиваю
Why do they say it’s expensive Well, if you get
А почему де говор дорого Ну это если
good teeth and let’s say you get free fillings,
хорошие же зубы ставить а бесплатные
stop stop
допустим пломбы ставить е стоп стоп
for free when you brushed your
бесплатно когда ты делал чистку
teeth this morning  not in the sense of
зубов сегодня утром не в смысле в
professional teeth cleaning in dentistry, I did
стоматологии профессиональную чистку
n’t just brush my teeth. Well,
зубов не просто чистил щёткой Ну я
somewhere, maybe four or 3 months
где-то ну возможно четыре или 3 месяца
ago, I put a filling. And I didn’t brush my teeth. I didn’t
назад ставил пломбу А чистку зубов Не не
do logs. Why would I?  I can
делал логи Да зачем если я могу здесь
brush my teeth here,
почистить зубы
look, I’ll explain it to you this way, and you
уся смотри объясню тебе так а вы каждый
do it every day What Well, what you
день это делаете Что Ну то что вы мне
just told me no, you don’t go through this procedure
сейчас сказали нет эту процедуру не
every day, I mean, look,
каждый день проходишь я в том что смотри
you brush your teeth every day Yes, but
ты каждый день чистишь зубы Да но всё
still there are some, you absolutely can’t do them
равно остаются ты не можешь их абсолютно
clean Yes, plaque still remains,
вычистить Да всё равно остаётся налёт
plaque accumulates, professional
налёт он накапливается профессиональная
teeth cleaning Yes, this is not for you, this is not
чистка зубов Да это тебе не это не
cleaned with a brush Yes, they specially apply a
щёткой чистят Да Это специально наносят
special substance that
такой специальное вещество которое
illuminates where it is, where this plaque is to
подсвет где это где вот этот налёт его
clean it off  it is cleaned with a special
счищать его счищается специальными
device like this Yes, this plaque is cleaned
приборчик такими Да счищается этот
from the teeth from this, uh, less like
налёт от зубов от этого э менее д как по
teasingly, the gums become irritated, then
дразнится раздражается дёсна потом
less caries can form Well, that
меньше образование кариеса може Ну то
is, uh, the teeth are healthier there, that is,
есть ээ зубы более здоровые туда то есть
you have never undergone this
ты никогда не проходил эту
procedure
процедуру
No So, why is it free and
Нет Так А почему это же бесплатно а
Thank you  I’ll do it for advice, just why in
Спасибо за совет сделаю просто почему в
Europe and here it is in Belarus, you can
Европе да и у нас он в Белоруси можно да
go and pay And they’ll do it for you, but in
пойти и заплатить И тебе сделают а в
Russia it seems like they do it for free, but they don’t
России вроде бесплатно но не
do it without a
делают без
clue And how old are you anyway, by the way
понятия А вам сколько вообще лет кстати
43 I understand A  What city are you in, what are
43 понял А в каком ты городе что
you saying about free dentistry? I’m
говоришь бесплатная стоматология Мне
now interested in there, and Tver said, and
сейчас интересно есть а Тверь сказал и
where are you getting your tooth treated for free there,
где ты бесплатно там полечить зуб вам
name the street right
прямо улицу назвать
now? Well, just
сейчас
a second. I just can’t understand if it’s
секунду Я просто не могу понять если э
free there, yes they do it, why I
бесплатно там да делают почему вот я
looked at so many dentists in this.
смотрел столько стоматологий в это в
Tver and everything is paid
Твери и все платный
Musorskogo street Musorskogo
Мусорского Мусорского
Yes street
Да улица улица
Musorskogo street
Мусорского улица
Musorskogo street is a
Мусорского это
masterpiece
шедевр улица
Musorskogo street What is there on Musorskogo street
Мусорского Что там на ули
clinic clinic What is the name Now
клиника клиника Как называется Сейчас
I’ll say
скажу
Musorskogo for everyone clinic for everyone yes
Мусорского для всех клиника для всех да
what is it  this is the kind of
это что это за
clinic
клиника
dentistry clinic for everyone Tver
стоматология клиника для всех Тверь
So who can tell us It’s free it’s
Так а кто нам скажет Она бесплатная она
in the Orbita business center Yes, what
в бизнес-центре Орбита находится Да что
about Musorskogo street 12 and the Orbita business center
о улица Мусорского 12 да бизнес-центра
Yes, well, you said the same thing to
Орбита Да ну вот вы же то то же самое
Musorskogo, also I’m joking
сказали Мусорского также это я сте баю
like  Mussorskogo I’m
типа Мусорского Я же
kidding I understand everything, this is private
прикалываюсь Всё я понял вот это частная
dentistry and for everyone this is
стоматология пи вот Для всех это частная
Mussorskogo’s private dentistry 12t
стоматология Мусорского 12т
this is not a free
это не бесплатная
state dentistry I don’t know they put me there
государственная не знаю мне там ставили
MBU free yes And how did you come and
МБУ бесплатно да А как ты пришёл и в
install a dentist for free in a paid clinic
платной клинике бесплатно поставил
No, they did a check for me first
стоматолога Нет мне проверку сначала
And then they said after 3 days
сделали А потом сказали через 3 дня
Come, they’ll put a bomb, but this is not a
Приходите бомбу ставят но это не
state clinic,
государственная ж клиника
no, but I’m interested Why
так нет а вот интересно А для чего
did businessmen set up a free
бизнесмены сделали бесплатную
clinic, you’re asking me  I
клинику вы у меня спрашиваете Я же вам
told you, they did it to me,
сказал шл мне сделали
maybe they sent you away from work or
Всё может тебя от работы направили или
your mother
мамка
paid you, well, how can I tell you,
заплатила Ну как вам сказать-то
ma, well, okay, how did you get to this particular
ма ну хорошо Как ты попал именно в эту
clinic, it was easy, you just came, everything, you just
клинику легко просто пришёл всё просто
came to the first clinic you came across, yes
пришёл в первую попавшуюся клинику да
Yes, I understand, she’s a paid clinic, but they
да понял она она клиника платная но тебе
did it for you for free, yes,
сделали бесплатно да
why did it all
почему всё
leak? The stories about free medicine
слился Байки про бесплатную медицину
ended on
закончились на улице
Musorskogo Street, damn it, no, Musorskogo Street
Мусорского блин не ну улица Мусорского
is
это улица
Musorskogo Street. Great
Мусорского Великая
Russian
русская
culture like squeak
культура лайк писка
comment write to th Telegram right now VN axis
комент пись на й Telegram прям зараз ось
apok tse more and more  respectfully YouTube took
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through skarg or in your ban and you
нас через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже
don’t show too many videos to people  We don’t always
багато вдео не показуе людям вчасно не
show information about streams for
показуе информация про стримы тому для
you, we Mali operational link to write
тоб мы Мали оперативный звязок пишиться
directly at the same time and Popik there in telegram
прямо зараз а Попик там в телеграми
okrim video sche tezh Tsikava and Korisna
окрим видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are guilty of you trimati
информация и мы повинни з вами тримати
postiyny operational link
постийний оперативный звязок
independantly in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава украини
letter
пись а